So friends, let's start today's video.
If you watch, we're going to
talk about NLC India, a government company. As
you might know, it's a
government company. It's believed the
government might launch an OFS (Offer for Sale) in this company. It's an
estimate, but
official news hasn't come yet. You
should know about this as well. Talking further about Angel One, you'll
know what the company does.
If you're in the stock market,
you'll definitely know about this company. It's a
broking platform. You
can see that there's been a
slight decline in the last few days.
And today, too, there was pressure on the
company. If you look at it, there's been an official announcement from the company. If you look at it, the
company isn't going to be
working in currency derivatives right now. The
company isn't going to be working in the currency derivatives segment. So, if
you look at it, there's been a slight decline. What will happen with this? It
means there will be a
slight impact on the business. Although it wo
n't be a huge impact, perhaps, but there will be a slight
impact.  It could happen because of this, perhaps
today the company's shares saw a decline
and if we talk further about ICICI Prudential
Insurance Company, then you know that it
is a very big insurance company and
if you look at it, you can see that the company has made a very big
announcement that if you
know then these insurance companies are so
big, that means they get so much
money, then where do they keep it, then
you must know that all the big
insurance companies invest that money and where will they invest it, of course it has to be done
in the share market only, that is, they do
some tax, so if you look at it, then
yes friends, we
need to know that right now and if we talk further about Tata Power
Company, then we can say that tremendous
news is coming out and if you look at it, then
Tata Power and Union Bank, yes
friends, if you look at it, Tata Power and Union Bank have entered into a
partnership and this is a
very tremendous thing, it is a great thing,
for whom it was done, you can also see that for rooftop solar
adoption, if you look at it, the company has entered into a
partnership, so what will happen to it,
You know that if you see, the government has
launched a new scheme, PM Surya Ghar
Free Electricity Scheme, so under this, if
you see, Tata Power, you know, does a
great job in rooftop, so
if you see,
Tata Power itself will give the option of Union Bank to finance it because if you
see, they have entered into a partnership, so if
you really go and see, if
you see, it is a
win-win situation for both the companies, for Union Bank as well as for
Tata Power, so the
consumers will also benefit a lot from this and if
you see, Tata Power
is definitely going to benefit along with Union Bank, so
you should know this as well and
if you do not have any idea, then let me
tell you that if you see, many big real estate
companies, if you see, they had
partnered with Tata Power in the past, that is, many months ago, like for
example, if you see, Godrej
Properties, which is a real estate company, had already
partnered with Tata Power, wherever
we have projects, you have to go there
and so
If Tata Motors wants to build a rooftop, they will approach
Union Bank for financing, and Union Bank will
also benefit. So, one can say that a good
synergy is going to be created in the future. If we
talk further, the name of this company is Bon
Dada Engineering. If we talk about this company, then
this company has also
made tremendous returns in a very short time. You
can see that the company has received another
order. You
can also see from where the order came from. If you see, the
company has received an order from Pace Digitech Infra Private Limited. You can see that the
order is worth about 24 crores. So
you should know this as well. The most important
thing is that the company is quite small and risky,
but
it is contributing tremendously in the segment it works in, the renewable segment.
You should also be aware of this. In the recent past, the company has made tremendous returns in a
short period of time.
If we talk further, the
name of this company is
ME Electronics Limited. If we
talk about this company, then
in the recent past, I have told you a lot about this company.  I had
mentioned that the company was in the news a lot
because if you look at the company, they had
said that they had developed a special
electric vehicle charger.
Because of this,
as soon as the company announced it, upper circuits started getting installed in the company
and after that,
lower circuits also started getting installed. For this,
I tell you that you should
not react immediately to news-based things. If
you talk about the latest news about the company, you can
see that the company has received a
new order and
from where, you can see that it has
received an order from the Mysore Division and the South Western Railway. So, this can be
said to be a very
good thing for the company. If you look further, the
company has received an order worth approximately Rs 1 crore 76 lakh. So,
you should know about this as well.
If we talk further about Gujarat Toolroom
Limited, then it means that this company was in the
news a lot. I mean, no
one knew about the company till a few days ago. And if we
look at today, we can say that
this company was in the news a lot and why it was there. So, you
can see that the company has received a lot of news.  A tremendous order has been
received and the biggest
thing is that if you see, the order is worth
90 million, the company has got the order and it is
working and if you see, you
can see that the company has got a new order and
from where it has been received, if you see that too, you can see that the company has got a
construction
order for the construction of coastal road,
so yes friends, if you see the order, you can see that the company has received an order
from Navi Mumbai
and you can see approximately it is worth 912 crores, yes friends, the company has received an
order worth approximately 912 crores, so you can say that it is a
very tremendous thing because it is a very big order
and the company is small, that means a small cap company, the
market cap of the company will be around 45000 crores
and it is a big thing that it has received an order of approximately 912 crores and it has got an order of approximately 912 crores, and it is a
big thing that it has received an order of approximately 912 crores and it has got this order from CIDCO, so
you should know about this too, so that's all for
now, thank you very much,
keep watching more such videos